<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mlf on Ksbigbass</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mlf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mlf on Ksbigbass</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mlf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FLW Losing?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/flw-losing-live-fans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/flw-losing-live-fans/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Is FLW losing the race for live view fans? More importantly are they losing the fight for fans?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social media is full of fans that want to watch live streaming bass fishing! We Love Bass Fishing! Streaming live fishing is quickly becoming an addiction for some, myself included.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;is-the-flw-losing-fans&#34;&gt;Is the FLW losing fans?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I sit here watching both the MLF Bass Pro Tour on one screen and BASS on another I wonder, why isn&amp;rsquo;t FLW broadcasting live?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLF Fishing Scale</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mlf-fishing-scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mlf-fishing-scale/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;fishing-scale-electrosamson-brecknell&#34;&gt;Fishing Scale: ElectroSamson Brecknell &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The MLF fishing scale: If you were wondering what that scale really looked like? This is the scale that has made the quick catch and release style tournament fishing the success it is. Now any club that wants to try and create their own MLF style tournament knows where to start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/MLF-scale.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;MLF Scale&#34;&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you like the way the MLF weighs the fish and then immediately releases it, then you are a fan of this scale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLF Shotgun Round 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mlf-shotgun-round-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mlf-shotgun-round-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MLF Shotgun Round 2 at Lake Chickamauga&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Apr 10, 2019 2:39 pm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;big-fish-being-caught-with-several-6-and-7-lb-fish&#34;&gt;Big fish being caught with several 6 and 7 lb fish!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In first is Cliff Crochet Cajun Baby on Fire thru the first 2 rounds 30lbs ahead of 2nd place!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fancasting a shallow grass filled area with a lipless rattle bait.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Crochet is concentrating on fish located in the scattered grass 10-15 ft off the bank.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;John Murray is 30 lbs back currently and in 2nd place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powroznik’s MLF: Wins Shearon Harris Reservoir</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/powrozniks-mlf-wins-shearon-harris-reservoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/powrozniks-mlf-wins-shearon-harris-reservoir/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MLF: Powroznik wins Major League Fishing stage 3 earning him the title of Bass Pro Tour Stage Three Champion. 63 - 04 was his final total weight. Landed 20 fish during the day with an average of 3.03 lbs and today&amp;rsquo;s biggest whopper was a badly needed 6.04.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLF or BASS or FLW</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mlf-or-bass-or-flw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mlf-or-bass-or-flw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;mlf-or-bass-or-flw-the-new-season-is-here&#34;&gt;MLF or BASS or FLW: The new season is here!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And a lot of changes have taken place over the off season. Seems like the new format of the MLF has taken over the bass fishing world. All the top level tour events have adopted some sort of catch and release system or soon will for the tournaments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is great for the conservation of the species and will cut down on mortality rates for sure. There&amp;rsquo;s no doubt that riding around in a livewell for up to 8 hours and then being put into weigh-in bags and flopped on a scale can be harmful to the days catch. If you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me you might miss the slaunches being held up on stage and the dramatic endings of the weigh-ins but doesn&amp;rsquo;t the long term health of the bass deserve more than that?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
