<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fish-Finders on Ksbigbass</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/fish-finders/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fish-Finders on Ksbigbass</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/fish-finders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on that graph?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-that-graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-that-graph/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-on-that-graph-we-have-all-said-that-one&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s on that graph? We have all said that one.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s on that graph? Fishing graphs are absolutely amazing pieces of hardware. Think about the abuse these things take. You would never leave an Ipad sitting outside in the temperature extremes you do with your fish finder. Much less strap it to the extreme environment of a boat going down the lake at 70 + mph. Takes a licken&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn what to look for on your fishfinders during the summer to find active fish that are readily available to bite. Once a school gets excited the action can last for hours. Actual pictures of on the water fish catches on the screen, just like a video game.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonar Units Truly are Becoming Fish Finders!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sonar-units-truly-are-becoming-fish-finders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sonar-units-truly-are-becoming-fish-finders/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sonar Units Truly are Becoming Fish Finders! I thought a Lowrance sonar video set would be appropriate for the blog this week.  Headed to Stockton Lake, Mo for this years championship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a 2 day event on a lake I have never been to before but know it&amp;rsquo;s been off limits for the past 30 days so no one else should have been either.  A lake this size and only 20 boats that made the championship, and the bumper boat session of last months small pond fiasco isn&amp;rsquo;t gonna happen!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
