<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summer on Ksbigbass</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/summer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Summer on Ksbigbass</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RE: The Hotter the Better</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/re-hotter-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/re-hotter-better/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/truck_temp_115.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Summer fishing in 115 degree temps. catching bass in 1 ft of water.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;115 degree summer temps&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Hotter the Better: Today was the hottest day on record in the area of Kansas that I live in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see by the picture it got to 115 degrees!  Not sure where you are from or have been but that is hot as hot gets in KS.  A few records we broken today as well as record numbers of 100+ days in a row. I did not have a surface water temp gauge with me but can only assume it was bath water warm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bass Fishing Wilson Lake, Kansas in July</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bass-fishing-wilson-lake-kansas-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bass-fishing-wilson-lake-kansas-in-july/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;bass-fishing-wilson-lake-kansas-in-july&#34;&gt;Bass Fishing Wilson Lake, Kansas in July&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wilson lake in Kansas is a very beautiful lake. It is surrounded by sandstone cliffs on a few sides and has sloping banks with easy shore access at other points, making it a popular recreation destination for many people in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WIth ultra clear water, someone could switch this out with the pool water at your house and you’d never know, except having smallmouth in your pool. Lol. Now this lake has all kinds of fish in it. It’s loaded with striped bass, hybrid bass, smallmouth bass, largemouth bass, and walleye too. I have spent hours catching striped bass and hybrids on virtually every cast in the summer months when they are feeding heavily on shad and creating topwater boils. There is a cliff for hang gliding, and mountain bike trails all around the lake which sponsor races year round.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buzzbait conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/buzzbait-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/buzzbait-conditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Buzzbait conditions: The conditions were perfect for a buzzbait bite — post-frontal with a nice chop on the water, just enough to break up the profile of my bait. It was a textbook presentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want the bass to eat topwater baits but I am not sure the conditions will allow, but if it does&amp;hellip;.Wow!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;buzzbait-conditions&#34;&gt;Buzzbait conditions:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;when-to&#34;&gt;When to:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Low skies, low light, and a slightly cooler day than you&amp;rsquo;ve been having, the topwater bite turns on&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underspin: Here&#39;s a better look</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/underspin-heres-better-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/underspin-heres-better-look/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Underspin. Here&amp;rsquo;s a better look. Turns out I was ahead of the curve on this one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bassmaster.com/anglers/casey-ashley&#34;&gt;Casey Ashley&lt;/a&gt; won the Bassmaster Classic on a very similar bait.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
