<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Top-Water on Ksbigbass</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/top-water/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Top-Water on Ksbigbass</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/top-water/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Z-MAN Pop Shadz Lures Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/z-man-pop-shadz-lures-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/z-man-pop-shadz-lures-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Z-MAN Pop Shadz Lures Review: This bait has a tendency to want to walk around on the hook. The trick to rigging this bait is to use a toothpick through the eye of the hook to hold it in place. This eliminates the bait moving around and causing headaches and anger.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;z-man-pop-shadz-lures-is-the-latest-in-weedless-topwaters&#34;&gt;Z-MAN Pop Shadz Lures is the latest in weedless topwaters.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the issue of the bait sliding down is resolved it will produce some nice fish for you. The weedless design makes it easy to throw it in areas you might be hesitant to throw a popper type bait with dangling treble hooks catching everything but bass. The Z-Man elastic design is tough and floats well. Very durable for sure. The light weight however can cause headaches casting into the wind on casting gear. The new Shimano Curado DC and its digital micro controller for the spool speed definitely helps out on backlashes for that situation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Missing a Key Element</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/not-missing-key-element/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/not-missing-key-element/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not Missing a Key Element: I am on my way to &lt;a href=&#34;http://goo.gl/maps/WisR&#34;&gt;Table Rock Lake&lt;/a&gt; for a Much needed week of fishing.    As I do my homework checking water levels, temps, and local guides fishing reports, I can&amp;rsquo;t quit thinking about throwing a gill painted topwater for some monster bass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/040.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Not Missing a Key Element&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not Missing a Key Element&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;so-i-ask__how-often-are-you-throwing-baits-that-imitate-sunfish&#34;&gt;So I ask _&amp;hellip;_How often are you throwing baits that imitate sunfish?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a reason fish biologists use sunfish as the primary food source for bass when stocking a pond. It&amp;rsquo;s as if bass live to eat them. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s bluegill, green ear or red ear sunfish, rock bass or pumpkinseed, all of these fish play a critical role in the diet of most bass throughout the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What about the Stalkers KVD?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-about-stalkers-kvd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-about-stalkers-kvd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-about-the-stalkers-kvd&#34;&gt;What about the Stalkers KVD?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Great Video where KVD talks about using a topwater popper!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-is-a-great-time-to-start-throwing-topwater-baits-start-in-60-degree-surface-water-temp-and-i-always-start-with-a-pop-r&#34;&gt;May is a great time to start throwing topwater baits, start in 60 degree surface water temp and I always start with a Pop-r.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/i-lA3KkqES0&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/i-lA3KkqES0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This video is such a great piece of info from one of the best.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But one big thing I think KVD fails to mention in this video is to watch for stalkers!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buzzbait conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/buzzbait-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/buzzbait-conditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Buzzbait conditions: The conditions were perfect for a buzzbait bite — post-frontal with a nice chop on the water, just enough to break up the profile of my bait. It was a textbook presentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want the bass to eat topwater baits but I am not sure the conditions will allow, but if it does&amp;hellip;.Wow!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;buzzbait-conditions&#34;&gt;Buzzbait conditions:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;when-to&#34;&gt;When to:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Low skies, low light, and a slightly cooler day than you&amp;rsquo;ve been having, the topwater bite turns on&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missed a Big One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/missed-a-big-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/missed-a-big-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Missed a Big One: Hit a local yocal today and found quite a few Big bucks running the bank.   Had about 20 min to fish, so I had to make the best of it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;targeting-spawning-flats&#34;&gt;Targeting spawning flats&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Started with a custom painted Pop-r and had a nice 8 lber blow up on it.  Being my first cast of the day I choked and yanked it out of his mouth !  ARGH!!  Missed a Big One!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
