<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tribute on Ksbigbass</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/tribute/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tribute on Ksbigbass</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/tribute/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extraordinary,  the fishing pole.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/extraordinary-the-fishing-pole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/extraordinary-the-fishing-pole/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;fishing-for-a-smile&#34;&gt;Fishing for a smile&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ordinary objects of resin, fiberglass thread, and bits of steel when combined can be used as an extraordinary tool to provide food for a family or it can transform a life through incommensurable ways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The origin of the fishing pole dates back about as far as history itself, first depicted in stone inscriptions found in Egypt, China, and Medieval England. Made from cane growing beside the river, a line was fashioned to the tip with a hook fabricated out of bone and tied to the end. Small worms, insects, minnows and frogs from the river were used as bait. Cane poles are as flexible as a gymnast and strong as an ox and can be made very long to reach farther out into the river with the bait. They were so productive at catching fish they are still sold at your local Walmart.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memorial Day Tribute: Folds of Honor.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/memorial-day-tribute-folds-of-honor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/memorial-day-tribute-folds-of-honor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Memorial Day Tribute: Folds of Honor. &lt;strong&gt;Memorial Day&lt;/strong&gt; is an American holiday, observed on the last Monday of May, honoring the men and women who died while serving in the U.S. military.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vimeo.com/253285064&#34;&gt;https://vimeo.com/253285064&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.foldsofhonor.org/about-us/&#34;&gt;Folds Of Honor&lt;/a&gt;: RETURNING HOME FROM HIS SECOND TOUR OF DUTY IN IRAQ, MAJOR DAN ROONEY, AN F-16 FIGHTER PILOT IN THE OKLAHOMA AIR NATIONAL GUARD, BECAME PAINFULLY AWARE OF THE REALITY FAMILIES FACE WHEN A LOVED ONE IN UNIFORM IS FALLEN OR DISABLED.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
