<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Summer on Ksbigbass</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/summer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Summer on Ksbigbass</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RE: The Hotter the Better</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/re-hotter-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/re-hotter-better/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/truck_temp_115.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Summer fishing in 115 degree temps. catching bass in 1 ft of water.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;115 degree summer temps&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Hotter the Better: Today was the hottest day on record in the area of Kansas that I live in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see by the picture it got to 115 degrees!  Not sure where you are from or have been but that is hot as hot gets in KS.  A few records we broken today as well as record numbers of 100+ days in a row. I did not have a surface water temp gauge with me but can only assume it was bath water warm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hotter The Better</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/re-the-hotter-the-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/re-the-hotter-the-better/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Re:The Hotter The Better: I fish all year round, weather conditions of all types. Here in Kansas, my current stomping grounds, the winters can be brutally cold, and the summers are hot. Tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s forecast is 110 degrees with 80%+ humidity..aaarrggghhh. A lot of the summer bass fishing articles talk about going deep, not this one. I am going to talk about fishing shallow with 90+ degree surface water temps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;946-degrees&#34;&gt;94.6 degrees&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That was the surface water temp last weekend, air temps where 106+ during the day and already 86 degrees at 5am on our way to the lake.  It was gonna be an extremely hot day but with a 20mph wind to help it would be bearable.  Hydration is talked about a lot for a good reason!  A day like that without a gallon of Gatorade in you and a severe heat stroke situation is truly possible.  I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen to many hospitals located lake side either&amp;hellip;just a friendly reminder&amp;hellip;Drink UP!  Might just save your life.  Back to the story and off the soap box.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bass Fishing Wilson Lake, Kansas in July</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bass-fishing-wilson-lake-kansas-in-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bass-fishing-wilson-lake-kansas-in-july/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;bass-fishing-wilson-lake-kansas-in-july&#34;&gt;Bass Fishing Wilson Lake, Kansas in July&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wilson lake in Kansas is a very beautiful lake. It is surrounded by sandstone cliffs on a few sides and has sloping banks with easy shore access at other points, making it a popular recreation destination for many people in the region.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WIth ultra clear water, someone could switch this out with the pool water at your house and you’d never know, except having smallmouth in your pool. Lol. Now this lake has all kinds of fish in it. It’s loaded with striped bass, hybrid bass, smallmouth bass, largemouth bass, and walleye too. I have spent hours catching striped bass and hybrids on virtually every cast in the summer months when they are feeding heavily on shad and creating topwater boils. There is a cliff for hang gliding, and mountain bike trails all around the lake which sponsor races year round.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big fish like big baits: Table Rock Locals May See Less Advantage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/big-fish-big-baits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/big-fish-big-baits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Big fish like big baits: Table Rock Lake is known for its spotted bass population as well as the quality largemouth and some giant smallmouth that show up from time to time. I&amp;rsquo;ve caught the biggest spotted bass of my life fishing there. As well as some picture worthy smallmouth. This is shaping up to be a great tournament with the largemouth bass on fire right now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;big-fish-like-big-baits-home-of-the-professional-anglers-association&#34;&gt;Big fish like big baits: Home of the Professional Anglers Association&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Home of the Professional Anglers Association&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Missing a Key Element</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/not-missing-key-element/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/not-missing-key-element/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not Missing a Key Element: I am on my way to &lt;a href=&#34;http://goo.gl/maps/WisR&#34;&gt;Table Rock Lake&lt;/a&gt; for a Much needed week of fishing.    As I do my homework checking water levels, temps, and local guides fishing reports, I can&amp;rsquo;t quit thinking about throwing a gill painted topwater for some monster bass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/040.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Not Missing a Key Element&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not Missing a Key Element&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;so-i-ask__how-often-are-you-throwing-baits-that-imitate-sunfish&#34;&gt;So I ask _&amp;hellip;_How often are you throwing baits that imitate sunfish?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a reason fish biologists use sunfish as the primary food source for bass when stocking a pond. It&amp;rsquo;s as if bass live to eat them. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s bluegill, green ear or red ear sunfish, rock bass or pumpkinseed, all of these fish play a critical role in the diet of most bass throughout the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What about the Stalkers KVD?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-about-stalkers-kvd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/what-about-stalkers-kvd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-about-the-stalkers-kvd&#34;&gt;What about the Stalkers KVD?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Great Video where KVD talks about using a topwater popper!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;may-is-a-great-time-to-start-throwing-topwater-baits-start-in-60-degree-surface-water-temp-and-i-always-start-with-a-pop-r&#34;&gt;May is a great time to start throwing topwater baits, start in 60 degree surface water temp and I always start with a Pop-r.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/i-lA3KkqES0&#34;&gt;https://youtu.be/i-lA3KkqES0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This video is such a great piece of info from one of the best.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But one big thing I think KVD fails to mention in this video is to watch for stalkers!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buzzbait conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/buzzbait-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/buzzbait-conditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Buzzbait conditions: The conditions were perfect for a buzzbait bite — post-frontal with a nice chop on the water, just enough to break up the profile of my bait. It was a textbook presentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want the bass to eat topwater baits but I am not sure the conditions will allow, but if it does&amp;hellip;.Wow!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;buzzbait-conditions&#34;&gt;Buzzbait conditions:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;when-to&#34;&gt;When to:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Low skies, low light, and a slightly cooler day than you&amp;rsquo;ve been having, the topwater bite turns on&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underspin: Here&#39;s a better look</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/underspin-heres-better-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/underspin-heres-better-look/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Underspin. Here&amp;rsquo;s a better look. Turns out I was ahead of the curve on this one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bassmaster.com/anglers/casey-ashley&#34;&gt;Casey Ashley&lt;/a&gt; won the Bassmaster Classic on a very similar bait.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/underspin.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;underspin: here&amp;rsquo;s a better look&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;underspin: here&amp;rsquo;s a better look&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Meat.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-meat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-meat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Meat.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today : May 7, 2011 2:53 am&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I fished for 2 hrs today in the afternoon.  The weather was the normal 25-40 mph South winds and a warm 76 degrees.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
